johnstonefitness.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy Policy - John Stone Fitness

You are here: [Home](http://www.johnstonefitness.com/) / Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Below you will find detailed information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit johnstonefitness.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This includes the ability to login to some of our features, such as the forums.

We also use third party advertisements on johnstonefitness.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can opt out of third-party vendor’s cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/).

You may chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
